<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[MLP] My Little RimPony - Medieval Overhaul Patches</name>
	<author>GeodesicDragon</author>
	<packageId>geodesicdragon.rimpony.medieval</packageId>
	<url>https://discord.gg/BGKnpza</url>
	<modVersion>1.27.3</modVersion>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>geodesicdragon.rimpony</packageId>
			<displayName>[MLP] My Little RimPony</displayName>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/GeodesicDragon/mylittlerimpony/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2349465544</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>DankPyon.Medieval.Overhaul</packageId>
			<displayName>Medieval Overhaul</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2553700067</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>geodesicdragon.rimpony</li>
		<li>DankPyon.Medieval.Overhaul</li>
		<li>imranfish.xmlextensions</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description><![CDATA[<b>ABOUT</b>
	
This mod contains a series of patches which will make My Little RimPony (MLRP) compatible with Medieval Overhaul.

<b>WHAT'S BEEN CHANGED?</b>
	
* Daybreaker recipes now use coal instead of chemfuel.
* Pawns in the Brony Community and Brony Xenotype scenarios start with plate armour instead of flak armour.
* Sweetie Bot turrets require a million watts of power.
* Poison joke joints can now be made at the workbench.
* Plushie benches no longer require power.
* Plushie benches are now built using iron bars and basic components.
* Plushie benches are unlocked after researching tailoring instead of electricity.
* Plushie benches can benefit from being near a tool rack.
* Brony traders and villagers are now equipped with peasant gear.
* Brony mercenaries have been converted into archers.
* Melee mercenaries are equipped with plate armour and zweihanders.
* Elite mercenaries and leader pawns are equipped with heavy armour and gunpowder weapons.
* Quick research projects have been changed to the Medieval tech level.
* Medium, hard and time-consuming research projects now require the advanced research bench instead of the high tech one.
* Hard and time-consuming research projects no longer require a multi analyser.
* Royalty DLC: Very hard research projects no longer require a multi analyser or techprints, but have been upgraded to the Spacer tech level.
* Royalty DLC: Very time consuming research projects no longer require a multi analyser or techprints.
* Mudbriar, Quibble Pants and Zephyr Breeze turrets now require a lot of power.
* Factions added by MLRP have had their tech levels changed to Medieval.
* The Stone Exchange no longer requires power.
* The Super Speedy Cider Squeezy 6000 no longer requires power.
* Nurse Redheart no longer requires power, but she will now spawn herbal medicine instead of industrial.
* The Fabric Exchange no longer requires power, and is unlocked once tailoring is researched.
* Vanilla Factions Expanded - Deserters: Requesting regular/critical intel now requires 50/100 herbal medicine.

<b>WHAT'S NEW?</b>

* Daybreaker has recipes to convert iron ingots into silver and back again.
* Daybreaker has recipes to convert Medieval Overhaul's basic components into base RimWorld components and back again.
* The Fabric Exchange has recipes to purchase linen, silk, daer leather, lindwurm scales, rox wool and tanning liquor.
* NPC factions - regular and batpony - will now send scholar caravans.

<b>WHAT'S REMAINED THE SAME?</b>

* NPC faction pawns are still equipped with the relevant plushies.

<b>WHY IS THIS A SEPARATE MOD?</b>

Because I'd rather give people the choice of having these changes, rather than force them by putting these patches in with the main mod.]]></description>
</ModMetaData>